<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Zoning (Hawaii County)</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/ParcelsZoning/MapServer/2</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/cty_zoning_haw.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata]  Description:  Hawaii County Zoning as of April, 2022.  Source:  County of Hawaii, Planning Dept. This Polygon feature data set was created by the County of Hawaii, Planning Department for approximate Zoning boundary location illustration use in permit reviews by the Planning Department. For additional information, please refer to complete metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/cty_zoning_haw.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.The County of Hawaii, Planning Department GIS data is intended to be used as a guide for planning purposes only and should not be used for boundary interpretations or other spatial analysis beyond the limitations of the data. Information shown on these maps are derived from public records that are constantly undergoing change and do not replace a site survey, and is not warranted for content or accuracy. The County does not guarantee the positional or thematic accuracy of the GIS data. The GIS data or cartographic digital files are not a legal representation of any of the features in which it depicts,and disclaims any assumption of the legal status of which it represents. This digital version is not the official map therefore users are advised to contact the County of Hawaii, Planning Dept. for zoning verification.For more detailed metadata information, please refer to the PDF text metadata document that is distributed with the GIS data.</abstract>
            <purpose>Hawaii County Zoning as of April, 2022</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Zoning</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii County</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii Island</themekey>
                <themekey>HawaiiStateGIS</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>Other Constraints</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning and Sustainable Development encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found. 
 Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and 
Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 
96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>County of Hawaii; Hawaii Statewide GIS Program</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20201030</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
